



# GABRIELA A. ESPINAL Property Management

smile to your new home

### Contact

551-998-7611

homesbygabby@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/gabrielaespinal

www.homesbygabbie.com

### Skills

Sales Marketing Real Estate Yardi Entrata MS Word MS Excel

## Certifications

#### Indeed

Computer Skills: PC Expert

Real Estate

Proficient

Customer Focus

& Orientation

Highly Proficient

#### LinkedIn

Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word Microsoft Outlook

# About me



Assistant Property Management with 5+ years of experience seeking new opportunities where my customer service background and education can be utilized to the fullest, providing customers with the highest quality of service and investors with a high rate of return on their investment. Hospitality Management Associate. Real Estate License in process. Personable, organized and task-oriented.

## **Experience**



### Lincoln Property Company

O Aug 2020-Present

Assistant Property Manager

Atlanta, GA, United States

- \*Responsible for implementing lease renewal and resident retention programs.
- \*Manage resident relations issues, which includes taking resident phone calls, requests and concerns.
- \*Analyze weekly leasing reports and forecast occupancy trends.
- \*Assist with developing and tracking marketing strategies, including advertising, promotions and publications.
- \*Manage rent collections, late notices and posting rent.
- \*Review and inspect vacancies, make-ready apartments and models.
- \*Inspect the property for community policy violations, needed repairs and overall landscaping.

### 1170 Apartment Corp

O Jan 2016 - Aug 2020

Assistant Property Manager

New Jersey, United States

- \*Help manage 26 Buildings for a total of 1170 units in a 35 acres land
- \*Advertise units and negotiate lease terms
- \*Perform tenant screenings
- \*Responsible for implementing lease renewal
- \*Collect rent on a monthly basis and handle late payments in a timely manner
- \*Maintain property by addressing tenant complaints, completing repairs, occupancy
- \*Create, mentor and manage a cohesive property maintenance team

### Smart Realty

O Jan 2019-Present

Property Sales Consultant / Leasing Specialist

New Jersey, United States

- \*Generating leads and turning them into opportunities for sales and rentals
- \*Contacting potential customers via telephone & email
- \*Arranging meetings with prospects in order to tour property
- \*Front office customer service
- \*Preparing lease documentation, property inspections, completing move-in and out paperwork and procedures

### Education



Real Estate

O Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Kovats Real Estate School

### Associate's Degree

O Dec 2010-Jan 2014

Hospitality Administration / Management Bergen Community College